Guide to the Oral History Project Documenting Yale University
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Wilkinson, John A., 2007 January 30
  After graduating from Yale College in 1960, Wilkinson worked for Yale for twenty-one years, 1960-1974 and 1981-1987. While studying for a Yale MAT degree awarded in 1963, he served as Assistant Dean of Freshmen and Assistant Master of Ezra Stiles College. From 1963-1974, he served as Dean of Stiles College, Assistant Dean of Yale College, and Associate Dean of Undergraduate Affairs. He left Yale in 1974 to become headmaster of the Hopkins School in New Haven. In 1979, he returned to Yale as University Officer for Development and Alumni Affairs, and in 1981 was appointed Secretary of the University. As Secretary he was Yale's chief liaison with the City of New Haven and represented Yale's administration on many issues of concern to on- and off-campus groups. In 1987, Wilkinson resigned to take a position as headmaster of the Germantown Friends School.
  - Interview, 1
    - Use copy, 1
  - Transcript, 1
    - Use copy (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Woodsum, Harold, 2008 November 30
  Director of Athletics, 1988-1994; Corporation Fellow, 1979-1988
  Harold E. "Ed" Woodsum graduated from Yale College in 1953 and from the Yale Law School in 1958. He later attended Westbrook College and earned a Doctor of Laws degree in 1991. He was co-founder and partner in a law firm from 1965-1988. Woodsum served on the Yale Corporation from 1979-1988, when he was appointed Director of Athletics.
  Football; Yale University -- Employees -- Labor unions; Students -- Political activity; Athletics; South Africa; Divestment; Brewster, Kingman, Jr., 1919-1988; Turner, Frank M. (Frank Miller), 1944-2010; Finnerty, Michael; Yale University. Committee on Investor Responsibility; Yale Corporation; Broude, Henry W.; Kagan, Donald; Vance, Cyrus R. (Cyrus Roberts), 1917-2002; Giamatti, A. Bartlett, 1938-1989; Gray, Hanna Holborn; Lamar, Howard Roberts, 1923-; Schmidt, Benno C., 1942-
  - Interview, 1
    - Use copy, 1
  - Transcript, 1
    - Use copy (Box 1, Folder 88)